let questionsOption = [
    {
        index:1,
        question:"What does HTML stand for?",
        answer:"hyper text markup language",
        options:[
            "hyper text preprocessor",
            "hyper text markup language",
            "hyper text multiple language",
            "hyper text multi language",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:2,
        question:"What does PHP stand for?",
        answer:"hypertext preprocessor",
        options:[
            "hypertext preprocessor",
            "hypertext programming",
            "hypertext preprogramming",
            "hometext preprocessor",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:3,
        question:"What does CSS stand for?",
        answer:"cascading style sheet",
        options:[
            "common style sheet",
            "colorful style sheet",
            "computer style sheet",
            "cascading style sheet",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:4,
        question:"What does SQL stand for?",
        answer:"structured query language",
        options:[
            "Stylish question language",
            "stylesheet query language",
            "structured query language",
            "statement question language",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:5,
        question:"What does XML stand for?",
        answer:"eXtensible markup language",
        options:[
            "eXtensible markup language",
            "eXecutable markup language",
            "eXamin multiple language",
            "eXtra multi-program language",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:6,
        question:"Which one is collective noun?",
        answer:"library",
        options:[
            "library",
            "captain",
            "girl",
            "doctor",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:7,
        question:"Which one is compound noun?",
        answer:"sunlight",
        options:[
            "bay of bengal",
            "team",
            "sunlight",
            "country",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:8,
        question:"Water has no color of its own.Here 'Water' is_",
        answer:"Material noun",
        options:[
            "Common noun",
            "Abstract noun",
            "Proper noun",
            "Material noun",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:9,
        question:"Which is the noun of 'Circular'?",
        answer:"Circle",
        options:[
            "Circulation",
            "Circle",
            "Circularly",
            "Encircle",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:10,
        question:"The correct noun of 'break' is_",
        answer:"breach",
        options:[
            "breakful",
            "breakdown",
            "breach",
            "breaking",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:11,
        question:"Which one is a material noun?",
        answer:"Brick",
        options:[
            "Brick",
            "Book",
            "Pirate",
            "Pack",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:12,
        question:"The word 'infantry' is a_",
        answer:"collective noun",
        options:[
            "abstract noun",
            "common noun",
            "collective noun",
            "material noun",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:13,
        question:"Which word falls under uncountable noun?",
        answer:"Water",
        options:[
            "House",
            "Poem",
            "Field",
            "Water",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:14,
        question:"Correct noun of the verb 'encourage' is_",
        answer:"courage",
        options:[
            "encourage",
            "courage",
            "courageous",
            "courageously",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:15,
        question:"What is the noun of 'Horrible'?",
        answer:"Horror",
        options:[
            "Horrify",
            "Horribility",
            "Horribly",
            "Horror",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:16,
        question:"What kind of noun is 'Herd'?",
        answer:"collective",
        options:[
            "collective",
            "proper",
            "common",
            "material",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:17,
        question:"The word 'compassion' is a/an_",
        answer:"Abstract noun",
        options:[
            "Abstract noun",
            "Concrete noun",
            "Proper noun",
            "Common noun",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:18,
        question:"Find the common noun among these_",
        answer:"Fish",
        options:[
            "Class",
            "February",
            "Fish",
            "Jute",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:19,
        question:"What kind of noun is 'Armies'?",
        answer:"common noun",
        options:[
            "abstract noun",
            "common noun",
            "material noun",
            "collective noun",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:20,
        question:"Which of the following is noun?",
        answer:"guise",
        options:[
            "practise",
            "advise",
            "guise",
            "advertise",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:21,
        question:"Synonym of 'audacious' is_",
        answer:"Valiant",
        options:[
            "Polite",
            "Cowardly",
            "Valiant",
            "Amity",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:22,
        question:"Synonym of 'avaricious' is_",
        answer:"Rapacious",
        options:[
            "Rapacious",
            "Local",
            "Magnanimous",
            "Antipathy",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:23,
        question:"Synonym of 'apocryphal' is_",
        answer:"spurious",
        options:[
            "genuine",
            "bona fide",
            "veracious",
            "spurious",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:24,
        question:"Antonym of 'Colossal' is_",
        answer:"Tiny",
        options:[
            "Cyclopean",
            "Cosmos",
            "Tiny",
            "Vast",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:25,
        question:"The word 'Cogent' means_",
        answer:"convincing",
        options:[
            "convincing",
            "irrelevant",
            "good",
            "precious",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:26,
        question:"____ is a scarcity or lack of something.",
        answer:"Dearth",
        options:[
            "Solvency",
            "Excess",
            "Dearth",
            "Pomp",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:27,
        question:"The antonym of deceitful' is_",
        answer:"honest",
        options:[
            "false",
            "honest",
            "delusive",
            "tricky",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:28,
        question:"Choose the right antonym of “Eclipse”_",
        answer:"brighten",
        options:[
            "dim",
            "blot",
            "darkness",
            "brighten",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:29,
        question:"Synonym of 'Emancipate' is_",
        answer:"liberate",
        options:[
            "bound",
            "enslave",
            "liberate",
            "conduct",
        ]
    },
    {
        index:30,
        question:"These ___ are mine. What will be the answer?",
        answer:"poultry",
        options:[
            "poultry",
            "poultries",
            "poultres",
            "poultrys",
        ]
    }
]